keralapals.com 2011-09-01

# privacy policy

Privacy Policy  
This is the privacy policy of keralapals.com. For more information on our privacy policy  you can contact us at keralapals @ yahoo.com . This statement provides you with types of data we collect from keralapals.com and how we are using it.

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes about your browser, IP address and your search term you used to come here . We collect no information on consumers who browse our Web page.

Cookies information:  We use cookies to store preferences to record information like what page users visit, browser type. and other information users sends .

Ad servers: To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and click stream information. For further information, consult the privacy policies of:  
http://www.google.com/  
http://www.cpxinteractive.com/  
[http://www.tribalfusion.com](http://www.tribalfusion.com/) etc

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**   
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  
 Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.   
 Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include

http://www.google.com/  
http://www.cpxinteractive.com/  
[http://www.tribalfusion.com](http://www.tribalfusion.com/) etc

If you are concerned about how your information is used, you can send email to the above email address.
